[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the second  song played on MTV?", "correct_answer": "You Better Run", "incorrect_answers": ["Hit Me With Your Best Shot", "Video Killed the Rock Star", "Radio Killed the Video Technician"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This planet of the Solar System was named after a Greek god of the sea and earthquakes. The name is actually the Roman translation of the gods name.", "correct_answer": "Neptune", "incorrect_answers": ["Mercury", "Pluto", "Uranus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This character, who becomes a psychopath as a result of a genetic experiment, is the villain in A View to a Kill.", "correct_answer": "Max Zorin", "incorrect_answers": ["Demetrius Xerxes", "Quentin Fremont", "Isidoro Ver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name for a vocal musical composition for between two and eight singers, written in the Renaissance and early Baroque eras and often performed without musical accompaniment?", "correct_answer": "Madrigal", "incorrect_answers": ["Magnificat", "Mass", "Mambo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does the kookaburra, a common Australian bird, get its name from?", "correct_answer": "The aboriginal name for it", "incorrect_answers": ["The food it eats", "Its appearance", "The sound it makes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the traditional Russian hot soup made of broth, beets, and tomato juice with various vegetables.", "correct_answer": "Borscht", "incorrect_answers": ["Rassolnik", "Shi", "Lapsha"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 2002 horror movie contains the quote, You start to play it and its like somebodys nightmare. And then this woman comes on, smiling at you, right? Seeing you...?", "correct_answer": "The Ring", "incorrect_answers": ["Saw", "Wrong Turn", "Darkness Falls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous book by British writer H.G. Wells presents the Martians as having octopus-like bodies?", "correct_answer": "War of the Worlds", "incorrect_answers": ["I Robot", "The Island of Doctor Moreau", "The Martian Chronicles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Napoleon\u2019s friend Deb selling door to door in the filmNapoleon Dynamite?", "correct_answer": "Key chains", "incorrect_answers": ["Candy bars", "Girl Scout cookies", "Vacuum cleaners"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Identify the 1982 movie from the quote: I know Im human. And if you were all these things, then youd just attack me right now, so some of you are still human.", "correct_answer": "The Thing", "incorrect_answers": ["Dawn of the Dead", "The Fog", "Alien"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what US state is the Fourpeaked Volcano, also known as Fourpeaked Mountain, situated?", "correct_answer": "Alaska", "incorrect_answers": ["Colorado", "Oregon", "Montana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The taste called umami, which is considered by the Japanese and Chinese taste researchers for one of the basic tastes, is mainly associated with which of the following groups of substances?", "correct_answer": "Proteins", "incorrect_answers": ["Carbohydrates", "Aldehydes", "Fats"]}]